别介
Don't
我说别介
I said "Don't"
谁呀？
Who's this?
是上帝吗？
Are you God?
我是中国人，所以你肯定是如来
I'm Chinese, so you must be Buddha.
但我在美国，所以你肯定是耶... 耶... 耶稣!
But I'm in the US, so you must be Je... Jesus... Jesus Christ!
我觉得如来肯定不会说英文
I don't think Buddha speaks English.
告诉我把我的小男孩儿
So tell me little boy,
为什么你试图在如此美好的一天自杀？
why are you trying to commit suicide on such a glorious day?
因为一切都再也没有意义了
Cause everything just doesn't make sense anymore.
一年，我特么用了一整年做的这个APP，
A year, I spent a whole fucking year building this APP,
到现在一个人也不愿意用
and now, not even a single person wants to use it.
太悲哀了！
So pathetic!
有点儿意思，那这个APP是干嘛用的呀？
Interesting, so what does this APP do?
是一款通过看电影来学英语的APP
It's an APP for learning English by watching movies you know.
它有这么一个让你感觉就像在和演员用英语对话一样的聊天模式
It has this amazing "Chat Mode" which makes you feel like you're talking with the actors using English.
而且这个APP前所未有地提供了所有能让你能更好理解电影的信息
And the app provides all the information you need to fully understand the movie, like never before.
比如语法、文化背景、冷知识
You know things like grammar, cultural references, trivia.
我意思是，这多棒啊！
I mean, how awesome this is!
好吧，听起来确实不错
Well, it sounds pretty good indeed.
这样如何？我会让每个看这个视频的人都去下载这个APP，
How about this? I'll make everyone who will be watching this video download your APP,
但是你得停止你这愚蠢的行为
but you need to stop this madness.
狗呼嘛？你当真会那样做？
Really? Will you do that?
会的，我的孩子
Yes, my son.
我爱你，上帝！
I love you, God!
我能... 我能再提一个愿望吗？
Can... Can I have one more wish?
啥？
Uh-huh?
你能升级一下我的电脑吗？
Can you upgrade my computer？
噢，你能修一下我的车吗？
Oh... Can you fix my car?
噢，等等，不不
Oh... Wait, no no.
你能帮我找个女朋友吗？
Can you find me a girlfriend?
女朋友？
A girlfriend?
连我都没有个该死的女朋友！
Even I don't have a goddamn girlfriend!
靠！
Damn it!